{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Stephenson_(police_officer)",
    "predicate": "property/office",
    "object": "resource/Commissioner_of_Police_of_the_Metropolis",
    "human_readable": "Paul Stephenson served as Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9786064028739929,
            "question": "Which city or region was Paul Stephenson responsible for as Commissioner of Police?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.949510931968689,
            "question": "During what time period did Paul Stephenson serve as Commissioner of Police?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9414259791374207,
            "question": "How did Paul Stephenson's role as Commissioner of Police impact the city or region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8446888327598572,
            "question": "What happened after Paul Stephenson finished his term as Commissioner of Police?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8362754583358765,
            "question": "Were there any notable events or challenges during Paul Stephenson's time as Commissioner of Police?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8218889832496643,
            "question": "Can you find any historical records or accounts about Paul Stephenson's time as Commissioner of Police?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7385378479957581,
            "question": "Who was Paul Stephenson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4967896342277527,
            "question": "What position did Paul Stephenson hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42364194989204407,
            "question": "What does 'Commissioner of Police' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41977810859680176,
            "question": "What are some of the responsibilities of a Commissioner of Police?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Stephenson served as Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_546_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'Commissioner of Police' refer to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_546_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position did Paul Stephenson hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_546_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Paul Stephenson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_546_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_546_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Sir Paul Stephenson was indeed the Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis, serving from 2009 to 2011."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Sir Paul Stephenson was appointed and served as the Commissioner of the Metropolitan Police. Therefore, the statement \"Paul Stephenson served as Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}